https://www.iescope.com/terms-and-conditions/

skip to Main Content
company /Terms & Conditions
Integrated Endoscopy Online Terms and Conditions
Your access to iescope.com is subject to the following terms and conditions, which may be updated by us from time to time without notice to you. By accessing or using this website, you agree that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound to these terms and conditions, as they may be amended from time to time, as well as to the terms of our privacy policy, which is hereby incorporated into these terms and conditions. You are responsible for periodically reviewing these terms and conditions for applicable changes. Your use of this website after posting by us of any changes to these terms and conditions constitutes your acceptance to those changes. If you disagree with these terms and conditions (as they may be amended from time to time), or are dissatisfied with this website, your sole and exclusive remedy is to discontinue using this site.
DISCLAIMERS
You acknowledge and agree that:
Although we strive to provide on this website the latest developments relating to our products and services, and other information about our company, we do not warrant the accuracy, effectiveness, and suitability of any information contained in this website. Each person assumes full responsibility and all risks arising from use of this Internet site. The information is presented “AS IS” and may include technical inaccuracies or typographical errors. Integrated Endoscopy reserves the right to make additions, deletions, or modifications to the information at any time without any prior notification.
INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY MAKES NO REPRESENTATIONS OR WARRANTIES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE WITH RESPECT TO THE INFORMATION OR CONTENT POSTED ON THIS WEBSITE. INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY HEREBY DISCLAIMS ALL REPRESENTATIONS AND WARRANTIES, WHETHER EXPRESS OR IMPLIED, CREATED BY LAW, CONTRACT OR OTHERWISE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, ANY WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY, FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE, TITLE OR NON-INFRINGEMENT. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND OR NATURE, INCLUDING, WITHOUT LIMITATION, DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL (INCLUDING LOSS OF PROFIT) CONSEQUENTIAL OR INCIDENTAL DAMAGES ARISING FROM OR IN CONNECTION WITH THE EXISTENCE OR USE OF THIS INTERNET SITE AND/OR THE INFORMATION OR CONTENT POSTED ON THIS WEBSITE, REGARDLESS OF WHETHER INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY HAS BEEN ADVISED AS TO THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES.
Integrated Endoscopy is not responsible, and provides no warranty whatsoever, for the accuracy, effectiveness, timeliness, and suitability of any information or content obtained from third parties, including any hyperlinks to or from third-party sites. Except as otherwise provided on this website, Integrated Endoscopy will not edit, censor, or otherwise control any content provided by third parties on any bulletin board, chat room, or other similar forums posted on its website. Such information should, therefore, be considered as suspect and is not endorsed by Integrated Endoscopy.
This website may contain forward-looking statements that reflect Integrated Endoscopy’s current expectation regarding future events and business development. The forward-looking statements involve risks and uncertainties. Actual developments or results could differ materially from those projected and depend on a number of factors including, but not limited to, the success of current research programs, results of pending or future clinical trials, ongoing commercialization of its products, regulatory approvals of pharmaceuticals, validity, and enforcement of its patents, the stability of its commercial relationships, and the general economic conditions. Integrated Endoscopy intends to update this site on a regular basis but assumes no obligation to update any of the content.
YOUR USE
You understand, acknowledge, and agree to the following:
By using this website, you agree not to disrupt or intercept our electronic information posted on this website or on any of our servers. You also agree not to attempt to circumvent any security features of our website, and to abide by all applicable, local, state, federal and international laws, rules and regulations.
You grant Integrated Endoscopy the right to use all content you upload or otherwise transmit to this website, subject to these terms and conditions and Integrated Endoscopy’s privacy policy in any manner Integrated Endoscopy chooses, including, but not limited, to copying, displaying, performing, or publishing it in any format whatsoever, modifying it, incorporating it into other material or making a derivative work based on it.
Except as expressly stated and agreed upon in advance by Integrated Endoscopy, no confidential relationship shall be established in the event that any user of this Internet site should make any oral, written or electronic communication to Integrated Endoscopy (such as feedback, questions, comments, suggestions, ideas, etc.). If any Integrated Endoscopy website requires or requests that such information be provided, and that such information contains personal identifying information (e.g., name, address, phone number), Integrated Endoscopy shall obtain, use and maintain it in a manner consistent with our privacy policy. Otherwise, such communication and any information submitted therewith shall be considered non-confidential, and Integrated Endoscopy shall be free to reproduce, publish or otherwise use such information for any purposes whatsoever including, without limitation, the research, development, manufacture, use or sale of products incorporating such information. The sender of any information to Integrated Endoscopy is fully responsible for its content, including its truthfulness and accuracy and its non-infringement of any other person’s proprietary or privacy rights.
INTELLECTUAL PROPERTY
The trademarks, service marks, trade names, trade dress, and products in this Internet site are protected in the United States and internationally. No use of any of these may be made without the prior, written authorization of the owners of this site, except to identify the products or services of the company.
PRIVACY AND SECURITY
Integrated Endoscopy is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. We understand the importance of privacy to our customers and visitors to our website. Our use of personally identifiable information is governed by our privacy policy and by accessing and using our website, you agree to be bound by that policy.
You recognize and agree that when submitting your personally identifiable information to sonexhealth.com, Integrated Endoscopy has safeguards in place to prevent unauthorized access or interception, there is no absolute guarantee of security. IN THE UNLIKELY EVENT OF AN INTERCEPTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS DESPITE OUR EFFORTS, INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY SHALL NOT BE RESPONSIBLE FOR SUCH INTERCEPTIONS OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, OR ANY DIRECT, INDIRECT, SPECIAL, INCIDENTAL, OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES (INCLUDING LOST PROFITS) SUFFERED BY A CUSTOMER OR USER, EVEN IF INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY HAS PREVIOUSLY BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF SUCH DAMAGES. INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY DOES NOT WARRANT, EITHER EXPRESSLY OR IMPLIEDLY, THAT THE INFORMATION PROVIDED BY ANY CUSTOMER SHALL BE FREE FROM INTERCEPTION OR UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, AND DOES NOT PROVIDE ANY IMPLIED WARRANTIES OF MERCHANTABILITY AND FITNESS FOR A PARTICULAR PURPOSE. EACH CUSTOMER IS RESPONSIBLE FOR MAINTAINING THE CONFIDENTIALITY OF HIS OR HER OWN PASSWORD.
LIMITATION OF LIABILITY
Integrated Endoscopy does not assume any liability for the materials, information and opinions provided on, posted to, or otherwise available through, this website. Reliance on these materials, information and opinions is solely at your own risk. Integrated Endoscopy disclaims any liability for injury or damages resulting from the use of this website, or the content contained thereon.
THIS INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY WEBSITE, THE SITE CONTENT, AND THE PRODUCTS AND SERVICES PROVIDED ON OR AVAILABLE THROUGH THIS WEBSITE ARE PROVIDED ON AN “AS IS” AND “AS AVAILABLE” BASIS, WITH ALL FAULTS. IN NO EVENT SHALL INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY, OR ITS SUBSIDIARIES, AFFILIATES, VENDORS, OR THEIR RESPECTIVE DIRECTORS, EMPLOYEES OR AGENTS (HEREINAFTER “INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY PARTIES”) BE LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGES OF ANY KIND, UNDER ANY LEGAL THEORY, ARISING OUT OF OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF, OR INABILITY TO USE, THIS WEBSITE, THE SITE CONTENT, ANY SERVICES PROVIDED ON OR THROUGH THIS WEBSITE OR ANY LINKED SITE, INCLUDING ANY SPECIAL, INDIRECT, PUNITIVE, INCIDENTAL, EXEMPLARY OR CONSEQUENTIAL DAMAGES, INCLUDING, BUT NOT LIMITED TO, PERSONAL INJURY, LOST PROFITS OR DAMAGES RESULTING FROM DELAY, INTERRUPTION IN SERVICE, VIRUSES, DELETION OF FILES OR ELECTRONIC COMMUNICATIONS, OR ERRORS, OMISSIONS OR OTHER INACCURACIES IN THIS WEBSITE OR THE SITE CONTENT, WHETHER OR NOT THERE IS NEGLIGENCE BY INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY AND WHETHER OR NOT INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY HAS BEEN ADVISED OF THE POSSIBILITY OF ANY SUCH DAMAGES. Some states do not allow the limitation of liability, so this provision may not apply to you.
PLEASE BE AWARE THAT ADDITIONAL LEGAL NOTICES, DISCLAIMERS, AND OTHER TERMS AND CONDITIONS MAY APPLY TO THIS AND OTHER WEBSITES OWNED OR OPERATED BY INTEGRATED ENDOSCOPY.
GENERAL
You agree that these terms and conditions describe the entire agreement between us with respect to its subject matter. iescope.com was created and is operated under the laws of the state of California. The laws of the state of California will control the terms and conditions provided in these terms and conditions, without giving effect to any principles of conflict of laws. If a court of competent jurisdiction finds that any provision of these terms and conditions is invalid or unenforceable, you agree that the other provisions of these terms and conditions will remain in full force and effect. You agree that regardless of any applicable law to the contrary, you cannot file a claim or cause of action arising out of or related to iescope.com or these terms and conditions more than one (1) year after such claim or cause of action arose.
© Copyright 2020 Integrated Endoscopy. All Rights reserved.
website: kressdesign.com
No part of this website may be reproduced without prior permission from Integrated Endoscopy.
